Mubassera Shaikh

To work with an organization that provides me an opportunity to grow & to exploit my potential to excel in the area of my preview so to help the organization in the accomplishment of its goal. Learning new innovative techniques with not only theoretical aspects but also its co-relation with practical situation and development through continuous improvement, teamwork and complete dedication, so as to contribute a fraction in the field of Clinical Research.

mubassera17@gmail.com

+91 7383180383

Satadhar, Sola, Ahmedabad

WORK EXPERIENCE

Clinical Research Coordinator

Occura Eyecare and Research Center

02/2021 - 05/2021,

Ahmedahad

Tasks

- Working in ophthalmic studies
- o SOP Writing, Coordinating with the CRO and PI

Executive Clinical Research Coordinator

Care Institute of Medical Sciences(CIMS) Hospital

03/2019 - 02/2021, Ahmedabad

Tasks

- o Previously worked in myocardial infarction, Heart failure, Valve replacement, stent device registry, HIV trials.
- o Works collaboratively with the other members of the team and the clinical and administrative support teams to ensure protocols are followed and that there us timely documentation and submission of study data.
- o Perform all duties and responsibilities in accordance with SOPs. Completion of source documentation on each study visits that is used to track all Study related activities so that time, effort and materials can be accounted for a monthly basis.
- Coordinate and attended sponsor site selection visits, Routine monitoring visits, and study close out visits.
- o Managing patient visit schedule. Maintain drug accountability records and other logs required as per protocols. Maintain Site Master File.
- o Completing of RDC/ eCRFs/CRFs in a timely manner. Respond to data clarification requests in a timely manner. SAE Reporting.
- Maintain excel sheet, tracking updates to database of all subjects enrolled on studies.
- o Communication link between CRO/Sponsor and investigator. Communication link between various departments of hospital.

Clinical Research Trainee

Care Institute of Medical Sciences(CIMS) Hospital

09/2018 - 03/2019. Ahmedabad

Achievements/Tasks

 Intensive training taken in CIMS SMO, EC, Medical Writing, Data Management department.

EDUCATION

Master of Science – Clinical Research

School of Science, Gujarat University

07/2017 - 05/2019, Ahmedabad

Bachelor of Science – Microbiology

J &J college of science, Gujarat University,

07/2014 - 04/2017, Nadiad

SKILLS



PROJECT WORK

The Impact of Blood Transfusion on outcomes in patient undergoing Coronary Artery **Bypass** Grafting (09/2018 - 03/2019)

Dissertation work done at CIMS hospital retrospective study which is based on CIMS Hospital data and I'm randomly choose 200 subjects of 2018, And my object is to find out the blood transfusion rate in CABG patients and factors affecting blood transfusion and outcomes in patients undergoing CABG

PUBLICATIONS

Review Article: International - 1

Citation of Review Article: Mubassera Shaikh, Parloop Bhatt, Kishor Gupta. SWOT Analysis of On pump and Off pump Coronary Artery Bypass Grafting Surgery; Volume 9, Issue 12, 420-428; ISSN 2278 – 4357; doi: 10.20959/wjpps202012-17658

LANGUAGES

English

Full Professional Proficiency

Full Professional Proficiency

Gujarati

Native or Bilingual Proficienc